final List<Map<String, dynamic>> generalQuestions = [
  {
    "question": "How many languages are there in the world?",
    "options": ["3544", "9127", "7164", "5823"],
    "answer": "7164"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which year was Rome founded?",
    "options": ["44 B.C", "166 A.D", "407 A.D", "476 A.D"],
    "answer": "44 B.C"
  },
  {
    "question": "What's the biggest city in the world by population?",
    "options": ["Mexico City, Mexico", "Tokyo, Japan", "Shanghai, China", "São Paulo, Brazil"],
    "answer": "Tokyo, Japan"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the phobia of open areas?",
    "options": ["Agoraphobia", "Claustrophobia", "Acrophobia", "Cynophobia"],
    "answer": "Agoraphobia"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the element with the highest atomic number?",
    "options": ["Tennessine (Ts)", "Oganesson (Og)", "Livermorium (Lv)", "Uranium (U)"],
    "answer": "Oganesson (Og)"
  },
  {
    "question": "What will be the fastest-growing economy in 2025?",
    "options": ["Brazil", "China", "Guyana", "Mexico"],
    "answer": "Guyana"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many symphonies did Beethoven compose?",
    "options": ["7", "8", "9", "11"],
    "answer": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the top scorer in FIFA World Cup history for men?",
    "options": ["Just Fontaine", "Gerd Müller", "Ronaldo Nazário", "Miroslav Klose"],
    "answer": "Miroslav Klose"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the percentage of years humans have lived on Earth compared to dinosaurs?",
    "options": ["19%", "5%", "1.7%", "0.13%"],
    "answer": "0.13%"
  },
  {
    "question": "How long does light take to reach Earth?",
    "options": ["Immediately", "About 2 Minutes", "About 8 Minutes", "One hour"],
    "answer": "About 8 Minutes"
  },
   {
    "question": "Which year did the second world war begin?",
    "options": ["1938", "1939", "1940", "1941"],
    "answer": "1939"
  },
   {
    "question": "What's the deepest lake in the world?",
    "options": ["Baikal", "Victoria", "Tanganyika", "Ontario"],
    "answer": "About 8 Minutes"
  },
   {
    "question": "If you devide 1 on Zero, you will get?",
    "options": ["Infinity", "0", "1", "Undefined"],
    "answer": "Undefined"
  },
   {
    "question": "How many letters in Greek langauge?",
    "options": ["24", "26", "28", "30"],
    "answer": "24"
  },
   {
    "question": "Who did invent typewriter?",
    "options": ["henry pascal", "Thomas edison", "Pellegrino Turri", "Johannes Gutenberg"],
    "answer": "Pellegrino Turri"
  }
];